School of Computing Science fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Curriculum and instruction files, 1970 - 1991; F-93-7; 1.82 m of textual records
  - Course files, 1973 - 1991; F-93-7-2; 1.63 m of textual records
    - CMPT 105-3 Introduction to Computing, 1984 - 1986; F-93-7-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 93-21)
    - CMPT 105-3 Introduction to Computing, 1987 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 93-21)
    - CMPT 110-3 Introduction to Computation in the Humanities, 1978 - 1983; F-93-7-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 93-21)
    - CMPT 111-1 Introduction to an Additional Programming Language - Cobol, 1989 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 93-21)
    - CMPT 112-1 Introduction to a Second Programming Language - C, 1988 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 93-22)
    - CMPT 113-1 Introduction to an Additional Programming Language - PL/I, 1989 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 93-22)
    - CMPT 114-1 Introduction to a Second Programming Language - Fortran 77, 1989 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 93-22)
    - CMPT 115-1 Introduction to a Second Programming Language - Pascal, 1988 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 93-22)
    - CMPT 118-3 Computing Projects in the Arts and Sciences, 1974 - 1975; F-93-7-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 93-22)
    - CMPT 118-3 Computing Projects in the Arts and Sciences, 1976 - 1978; F-93-7-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 93-22)
    - CMPT 118-3 Computing Projects in the Arts and Sciences, 1979 - 1981; F-93-7-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 93-22)
    - CMPT 118-3 Computing Projects in the Arts and Sciences, 1982 - 1985; F-93-7-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 93-22)
    - CMPT 121-1 Computing Project, 1982; F-93-7-2-0-38 (Archival box - standard 93-22)
    - CMPT 142-1 Computing Project - Kinesiology, 1977 - 1978; F-93-7-2-0-39 (Archival box - standard 93-22)
    - CMPT 142-3 Computing Project in Kinesiology, 1979 - 1982; F-93-7-2-0-40 (Archival box - standard 93-22)
    - CMPT 171-1 Computing Project - Business Administration, 1982; F-93-7-2-0-41 (Archival box - standard 93-22)
    - CMPT 201-3 Data and Program Organization, 1973 - 1977; F-93-7-2-0-42 (Archival box - standard 93-22)
    - CMPT 201-3 Data and Program Organization, 1978 - 1988; F-93-7-2-0-43 (Archival box - standard 93-22)
    - CMPT 201-3 Data and Program Organization, 1989 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-44 (Archival box - standard 93-23)
    - CMPT 205-3 Introduction to Formal Topics in Computing Science, 1977 - 1981; F-93-7-2-0-45 (Archival box - standard 93-23)
    - CMPT 205-3 Introduction to Formal Topics in Computing Science, 1982 - 1989; F-93-7-2-0-46 (Archival box - standard 93-23)
    - CMPT 205-3 Introduction to Formal Topics in Computing Science, 1990 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-47 (Archival box - standard 93-23)
    - CMPT 218-3 Special Topics: Programming and Software for Business Students, 1977 - 1984; F-93-7-2-0-48 (Archival box - standard 93-23)
    - CMPT 240-3 Computing in the Life Sciences, 1979; F-93-7-2-0-49 (Archival box - standard 93-23)
    - CMPT 250-3 Computer Uses in Environmental Studies, 1981; F-93-7-2-0-50 (Archival box - standard 93-23)
    - CMPT 260-3 Social Implications of Computer Technology, 1976 - 1985; F-93-7-2-0-51 (Archival box - standard 93-23)
    - CMPT 275-3 Software Engineering, 1985 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-52 (Archival box - standard 93-23)
    - CMPT 280-3 Computation in the Humanities I, 1977; F-93-7-2-0-53 (Archival box - standard 93-23)
    - CMPT 283-3 Programming Languages, 1977 - 1981; F-93-7-2-0-54 (Archival box - standard 93-24)
    - CMPT 290-3 Digital Circuits and Systems, 1977 - 1982; F-93-7-2-0-55 (Archival box - standard 93-24)
    - CMPT 290-3 Digital Circuits and Systems, 1983 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-56 (Archival box - standard 93-24)
    - CMPT 291-3 Analogue and Digital Circuits, 1977 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-57 (Archival box - standard 93-24)
    - CMPT 293-3 Introduction to Minicomputers and Microprocessors, 1979; F-93-7-2-0-58 (Archival box - standard 93-24)
    - CMPT 300-3 Introduction to Operating Systems, 1990 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-59 (Archival box - standard 93-24)
    - CMPT 301-3 Applied Programming I, 1975 - 1979; F-93-7-2-0-60 (Archival box - standard 93-24)
    - CMPT 301-3 System Development Methodology / Management of Information Systems, 1980 - 1989; F-93-7-2-0-61 (Archival box - standard 93-25)
    - CMPT 301-3 Information Management Systems, 1990; F-93-7-2-0-62 (Archival box - standard 93-25)
    - CMPT 302-3 Applied Programming II / System Development Methodology II, 1976 - 1983; F-93-7-2-0-63 (Archival box - standard 93-25)
    - CMPT 305-3 Computer Simulation and Modelling, 1976 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-64 (Archival box - standard 93-25)
    - CMPT 307-3 Data Structures and Algorithms, 1987 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-65 (Archival box - standard 93-25)
    - CMPT 315-2 Advanced Software Project, 1978 - 1987; F-93-7-2-0-66 (Archival box - standard 93-25)
    - CMPT 320-3 Social Implications of a Computerized Society, 1985 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-67 (Archival box - standard 93-25)
    - CMPT 340-3 Computers in Biomedicine, 1982 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-68 (Archival box - standard 93-25)
    - CMPT 350-3 Information and Public Policy, 1975 - 1990; F-93-7-2-0-69 (Archival box - standard 93-25)
    - CMPT 351-3 Computer Graphics I: Linear Graphs / Introduction to Computer Graphics, 1976 - 1979; F-93-7-2-0-70 (Archival box - standard 93-25)
    - CMPT 351-3 Introduction to Computer Graphics, 1980 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-71 (Archival box - standard 93-26)
    - CMPT 354-3 Information and Organization Retrieval / File and Database Structure, 1976 - 1982; F-93-7-2-0-72 (Archival box - standard 93-26)
    - CMPT 354-3 File and Database Structure / Database Systems and Structures, 1983 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-73 (Archival box - standard 93-26)
    - CMPT 360-3 Computing for Statistical Data Processing, 1978 - 1979; F-93-7-2-0-74 (Archival box - standard 93-26)
    - CMPT 362-4 Educational Uses of Computers / Computers in Education, 1974 - 1988; F-93-7-2-0-75 (Archival box - standard 93-26)
    - CMPT 370-3 Management and Information Systems I / Information Systems Design, 1975 - 1982; F-93-7-2-0-76 (Archival box - standard 93-26)
    - CMPT 370-3 Information System Design, 1983 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-77 (Archival box - standard 93-26)
    - CMPT 371-3 Management and Information System, 1976 - 1987; F-93-7-2-0-78 (Archival box - standard 93-26)
    - CMPT 371-3 Data Communications / Data Communications and Networking, 1988 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-79 (Archival box - standard 93-27)
    - CMPT 380-3 Computation in the Humanities II: Computational Linguistics, 1978 - 1986; F-93-7-2-0-80 (Archival box - standard 93-27)
    - CMPT 383-3 Comparative Programming Languages, 1982 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-81 (Archival box - standard 93-27)
    - CMPT 384-3 Symbolic Computing, 1984 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-82 (Archival box - standard 93-27)
    - CMPT 390-3 Digital Circuits and Systems, 1976 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-83 (Archival box - standard 93-27)
    - CMPT 391-3 Microcomputer Hardware Workshop, 1982 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-84 (Archival box - standard 93-27)
    - CMPT 392-3 Introduction to Digital Signal Processing, 1985; F-93-7-2-0-85 (Archival box - standard 93-27)
    - CMPT 393-3 Systems Software for Minicomputers and Microcomputers, 1982 - 1986; F-93-7-2-0-86 (Archival box - standard 93-27)
    - CMPT 400-3 Hardware-Software Architecture I, 1975 - 1990; F-93-7-2-0-87 (Archival box - standard 93-27)
    - CMPT 401-3 Hardware-Software Architecture II / Operating Systems, 1976 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-88 (Archival box - standard 93-27)
    - CMPT 402-3 Operating Systems Software Laboratory, 1987 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-89 (Archival box - standard 93-27)
    - CMPT 404-4 Computer System Measurement and Evaluation, 1975 - 1984; F-93-7-2-0-90 (Archival box - standard 93-27)
    - CMPT 405-3 Design and Analysis of Computer Algorithms, 1979 - 1990; F-93-7-2-0-91 (Archival box - standard 93-27)
    - CMPT 406-3 Computational Geometry, 1984 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-92 (Archival box - standard 93-27)
    - CMPT 410-4 Artificial Intelligence, 1976 - 1979; F-93-7-2-0-93 (Archival box - standard 93-28)
    - CMPT 410-4 Artificial Intelligence, 1980 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-94 (Archival box - standard 93-28)
    - CMPT 411-5 Expert Systems and Knowledge Representation / Projects / Practicums, 1975 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-95 (Archival box - standard 93-28)
    - CMPT 412-3 Computational Vision, 1987 - 1990; F-93-7-2-0-96 (Archival box - standard 93-28)
    - CMPT 413-3 Computational Linguistics, 1987 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-97 (Archival box - standard 93-28)
    - CMPT 414-3 Model-Based Computer Vision, 1990 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-98 (Archival box - standard 93-28)
    - CMPT 415-3 Special Research Projects, 1974 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-99 (Archival box - standard 93-28)
    - CMPT 416-5 Special Research Projects II, 1977 - 1990; F-93-7-2-0-100 (Archival box - standard 93-28)
    - CMPT 418-3 Special Topics in Computing Science I, 1976 - 1979; F-93-7-2-0-101 (Archival box - standard 93-28)
    - CMPT 418-3 Special Topics in Computing Science I, 1980 - 1989; F-93-7-2-0-102 (Archival box - standard 93-28)
    - CMPT 419-3 Expert Systems / Special Topics in Artificial Intelligence, 1989 - 1990; F-93-7-2-0-103 (Archival box - standard 93-28)
    - CMPT 451-3 Advanced Graphics / Interactive Graphics and Animation Systems, 1978 - 1990; F-93-7-2-0-104 (Archival box - standard 93-28)
    - CMPT 459 Special Topics in Database Systems, 1988 - 1990; F-93-7-2-0-105 (Archival box - standard 93-28)
    - CMPT 479 Real-Time Computing, 1987; F-93-7-2-0-106 (Archival box - standard 93-28)
    - CMPT 483-3 Compiler Construction, 1982 - 1990; F-93-7-2-0-107 (Archival box - standard 93-28)
    - CMPT 489 Special Topics in Programming Languages; Functional Programming, 1988 - 1990; F-93-7-2-0-108 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 490-3 VLSI Systems Design, 1987 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-109 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 491-3 Computers in Real Time Experiments / Analogue and Digital Circuits, 1976 - 1986; F-93-7-2-0-110 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 492 Microprogramming and Emulation, 1982; F-93-7-2-0-111 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 493/494 Colloquium in Interdisciplinary Topics I/II, 1975 - 1979; F-93-7-2-0-112 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 493/494 Colloquium in Interdisciplinary Topics I/II, 1980 - 1984; F-93-7-2-0-113 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 495 Digital System Design and Specification Laboratory I, 1983 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-114 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 496 Projects, 1991; F-93-7-2-0-115 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 499 Special Topics in Computer Hardware, 1987 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-116 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 601-5 Computing Science Education I, 1985 - 1992; F-93-7-2-0-117 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 602 Computer in Education, 1986 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-118 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 720-3 Artificial Intelligence, 1990; F-93-7-2-0-119 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 730 Foundations of Programming Languages, 1990 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-120 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 750 Computer Architecture, 1990; F-93-7-2-0-121 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 760 Operating Systems Design, 1990; F-93-7-2-0-122 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 810 The Design and Analysis of Algorithms, 1980 - 1989; F-93-7-2-0-123 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 811 Distributed Algorithms, 1989 - 1990; F-93-7-2-0-124 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 812 Parallel Computation, 1987; F-93-7-2-0-125 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 813 Computational Geometry, 1987; F-93-7-2-0-126 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 820-3 Artificial Intelligence, 1984 - 1989; F-93-7-2-0-127 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 821 Computational Vision / Pattern Recognition and Image Processing, 1981 - 1989; F-93-7-2-0-128 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 822 Computational Vision, 1986 - 1990; F-93-7-2-0-129 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 823 Formal Topics in Knowledge Representation, 1989; F-93-7-2-0-130 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 824 Logic Programming and Fifth Generation Computing, 1989; F-93-7-2-0-131 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 830 Compiler Construction, 1986; F-93-7-2-0-132 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 840-3 Advanced Topics in Simulation and Modelling, 1981; F-93-7-2-0-133 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 841 Database Design, 1983 - 1989; F-93-7-2-0-134 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 842 Distributed Computing, 1984 - 1989; F-93-7-2-0-135 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 843 Principles of Database and Knowledge-Based Systems, 1990; F-93-7-2-0-136 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 850 Current Topics in Computer Architecture, 1980 - 1985; F-93-7-2-0-137 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 851 Reliable and Fault-Tolerant Computing, 1983 - 1986; F-93-7-2-0-138 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 852 VLSI Systems Design, 1984 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-139 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 860-3 Algorithms of Optimization, 1981 - 1984; F-93-7-2-0-140 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 861-3 Biomedical Computing, 1982; F-93-7-2-0-141 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 862 Computer Mapping, 1980; F-93-7-2-0-142 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 863 Principles of Computer-Aided Design, 1982 - 1986; F-93-7-2-0-143 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 881-3 Database Design / Topics in Theoretical Computing Science, 1981 - 1990; F-93-7-2-0-144 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 882 Formal Topics in Knowledge Representation / Artificial Intelligence, 1986 - 1990; F-93-7-2-0-145 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 883 Special Topics in Programming Languages, 1986 - 1989; F-93-7-2-0-146 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 884 Principles of Database and Knowledge-Base Systems, 1989; F-93-7-2-0-147 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 885 Special Topics in Computer Architecture, 1987 - 1989; F-93-7-2-0-148 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 886 Special Topics in Operating Systems, 1983 - 1989; F-93-7-2-0-149 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 887 Hardware Architecture, 1984; F-93-7-2-0-150 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 891 Distributed Computing and Transaction Processing, 1983 - 1986; F-93-7-2-0-151 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 892 Diagnosis and Reliable Design of VLSI Systems / Special Topics, 1983; F-93-7-2-0-152 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 894-3 Directed Studies: Array Algorithms for APL, 1980; F-93-7-2-0-153 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
    - CMPT 895 Graduate Course on Database Design, 1980; F-93-7-2-0-154 (Archival box - standard 93-29)
- Publications, 1973 - 1999; F-93-8; 5 cm of textual records
  Series consists of publications created by the School and its predecessors. Material includes annual reports, Computing Science Student Society newsletters, course guides and brochures, graduate studies program guide and student handbook, and research overview report.
  For detailed records on courses described in the course guides and brochures, see "Course files" (sub-series F-93-7-2).
  The files are open with no restrictions.
  - Departmental Annual Reports, 1981 - 1984; F-93-8-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 93-16)
  - Computing Science Student Society newsletters, 1976 - 1977; F-93-8-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 93-16)
  - Course guides and brochures, 1973 - 1997; F-93-8-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 93-16)
  - Graduate Student Handbook / Graduate Studies Program Guide, 1985 - 1986; F-93-8-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 93-16)
  - Laboratory for Computer and Communications Research (LCCR) Annual Report, 1987; F-93-8-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 93-16)
  - School of Computing Science Research Review / Research Overview, 1990 - 1999; F-93-8-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 93-16)